为了从一个应用程序中获取它的开放气象图数据，
To fetch the data from open weather map within an
首先我们需要以URL的形式，
app, first we need to make an HTTP request to the
向API构造一个HTTP请求。
API at the URL that we decided on earlier. Then we
我们需要从输入流中以JSON字符串的形式读取响应。
need to read the response from the input stream to get
如果它没有被解析，那么我们需要检查一下是否哪里出现了问题。
a JSON string. It hasn't been parsed yet, but we'll worry
接下来，我们需要清空断开的连接，
about that later. Then we clean up by disconnecting the connection
并关闭一切输入流。我们也记录了我们所抓获的任何出错点。
and closing any input streams. We also log any errors that
由于这是一个庞大的网络公式化代码，
we catch. Since it's a lot of networking boiler plate code,
我们将为您提供的这些功能的代码。
we've provided you with a code snippet
请参阅下方的GitHub链接的简介。
that handles these steps. See the link for
当你已经看完，
the GitHub gist below. After you've taken a
点击此框，继续往下学习。
look at it, check this box to continue.